const questions = {
    lesson: [
        {
            write_in_capital_letters: [
                {
                    question: "dog .......",
                    answer: "DOG"
                },
                {
                    question: "apple .......",
                    answer: "APPLE"
                },
                {
                    question: "cat .......",
                    answer: "CAT"
                },
                {
                    question: "glass .......",
                    answer: "GLASS"
                },
                {
                    question: "umbrella .......",
                    answer: "UMBRELLA"
                },
                {
                    question: "jam .......",
                    answer: "JAM"
                },
                {
                    question: "train .......",
                    answer: "TRAIN"
                },
                {
                    question: "lemon .......",
                    answer: "LEMON"
                },
                {
                    question: "watch .......",
                    answer: "WATCH"
                },
                {
                    question: "queen.......",
                    answer: "QUEEN"
                },
                {
                    question: "bird .......",
                    answer: "BIRD"
                },
            ],
            fill_in_a_or_an: [
                {
                    question: ".......dog",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......fish",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......snake",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......elephant",
                    answer: "an"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......owl",
                    answer: "an"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......horse",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......frog",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......donkey",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......insect",
                    answer: "an"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......bird",
                    answer: "a"
                },
                {
                    question: ".......ant",
                    answer: "an"
                },
            ],
            circle_the_odd_word_out: [
                {
                    question: {
                        A: "a umbrella",
                        B: "a hat",
                        C: "a girl",
                    },
                    answer: "umbrella"
                },
                {
                    question: {
                        A: "a pineapple",
                        B: "a cake",
                        C: "a ice cream",
                    },
                    answer: "ice cream"
                },
                {
                    question: {
                        A: "an horse",
                        B: "an ostrich",
                        C: "an ant",
                    },
                    answer: "horse"
                },
                {
                    question: {
                        A: "a mouse",
                        B: "a cat",
                        C: "a owl",
                    },
                    answer: "owl"
                },
                {
                    question: {
                        A: "an ant",
                        B: "an donkey",
                        C: "an elephant",
                    },
                    answer: "donkey "
                },
                {
                    question: {
                        A: "an orange",
                        B: "an lemon",
                        C: "an apple",
                    },
                    answer: "lemon"
                },
            ],
            match_1_10_with_a_j: {
                A: ["1. dog", "2. umbrella", "3. apple", "4. fish", "5.snake", "6. orange", "7. bird", "8. ant", "9. frog", "10. lemon"],
                B: ["a. con rắn", "b. con ếch", "c. quả cam", "d. quả chanh", "e. con chó", "f. cái ô", "g. con kiến", "h. con cá", "i. con chim", "j. quả táo"],
                answer: ["1-e", "2-f", "3-j", "4-h", "5-a", "6-c", "7-j", "8-g", "9-b", "10-d"]
            },
            choose_the_correct_answer: [
                {
                    question: "What is the highest among the answer below?",
                    answer: "B",
                    A: "5 centimeters",
                    B: "20 meters",
                    C: "200 centimeters",
                    D: "100 decimeters"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "What was the matter with him? He........ a toothache",
                    answer: "D",
                    A: "to have   ",
                    B: "have",
                    C: "has",
                    D: "had"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "What subject is he......... now? Vietnamese.",
                    answer: "c",
                    A: "to learn",
                    B: "learn",
                    C: "learning",
                    D: "learned"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "............ did she go yesterday morning? She went to the bookshop.",
                    answer: "B",
                    A: "What",
                    B: "Where",
                    C: "When",
                    D: "Why"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "Are you free........ the evening? Yes, I am.",
                    answer: "B",
                    A: "in",
                    B: "on",
                    C: "at",
                    D: "to"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "She is going to......... television tonight.",
                    answer: "D",
                    A: "sing",
                    B: "play",
                    C: "stay",
                    D: "watch"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "............ is that ? It's my teacher.",
                    answer: "B",
                    A: "What",
                    B: "Who",
                    C: "Where",
                    D: "How"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "Does she like sandwiches ?......................",
                    answer: "C",
                    A: "Yes, she do",
                    B: "Yes, she is",
                    C: "Yes, she does",
                    D: "Yes, she like"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "This is Mai.............. mother is a doctor.",
                    answer: "C",
                    A: "his",
                    B: "she",
                    D: "her",
                    C: "he"
                  },
                  {
                    question: "She............. a banana.",
                    answer: "B",
                    A: "wants",
                    B: "want",
                    C: "to want",
                    D: "wantes"
                  }
            ]
        }
    ]
}

module.exports = {
    questions
};
